

Vali Rafinia

Naser.r@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/nrafinia https://naser.rafinia.info +98 912 7250317 Tehran, Iran

Summary

I am a senior software developer with over 10, years of experience. Working in various roles, from a junior developer to a team lead and IT department manager, has given me a great deal of experience. I am a success-oriented engineer focused on delivery and a great team player.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Principal Software Engineer

Iranian Internet Marketplace • Sep 2016 - present

- Designing the architecture and creating a new B2B panel for the company, providing the possibility of 2000% sales growth.
- Migrating the panel with microservice structure through Ocelot API Gateway, resulting in increased number of simultaneous users to 700 and active users to 20,000 per day.
- Design, develop, test, and maintain features like buying a flight, bus, train ticket online, Access control panel, admin section, etc.
- Designing and developing a new PWA UI via Blazor
- Providing REST API services for mobile application
- Optimizing search engine structure with Elasticsearch and increasing search output from 10 seconds to less than 0.5 seconds

Environment: C#, Asp.Net core 5.0, Blazor, Ocelot API Gateway, Redis, Elasticsearch, gRPC, JWT Token, MediatR, SQL Server, xUnit for Testing

Software Development Manager

TAK Makaron • Jul 2014 - Oct 2016

- Defining the road map and vision of the product within the team
- Helping team to resolve issues and remove any obstacles or bottlenecks
- Reviewing and improving team strategies regarding delivering features or production incidents
- Enabling multi-branch support instead of legacy single branch support through upgrading the whole project
- $\bullet~$ Upgrading the technology and structures in the system to increase system output by 40%
- Creating a system for collecting and transferring information from branches to the head office and vice versa

Environment: C#, Windows form, WCF, ADO.Net, SQL Server, SQL row versioning

Head of IT Research and Development Division

Solico Group • Nov 2012 - Oct 2014

- Investigating pros and cons of different solutions available in the market and third-party software and see which one fits best into the current company ecosystem
- Installation of MS Dynamics AX software and adding localization features such as solar calendar, RTL, ...
- Installation and management of Jira software along with localization such as solar calendar, RTL, ...

Environment: Java, X++ scripting language

Senior Software Engineer

Mandegar Group • Jan 2012 - Jul 2012

- Due to the insufficient efficiency of the financial and administrative system in the company, with the help of the team, I migrated the system from Delphi To ASP.Net.
- Support and maintenance of the legacy Delphi system until the full transfer to the new version

Environment: C#, ASP.Net form, LINQ to SQL, Delphi, SQL Server

Senior Software Developer

Neda Pardaz Informatic • Apr 2010 - Jan 2012

- Create a VOIP-based financial payment system for Sepah, Mellat, and Tejarat banks
- Support and maintenance of the legacy Delphi-based system

Environment: C#, Windows service, Delphi, SQL Server

More experience in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nrafinia/

EDUCATION

Islamic Azad University

Associate's Degree, Software

SKILLS

- .Net Technologies: .Net Core, ASP.Net, MVC, Blazor, Web API
- Programming languages: C#, JavaScript, T-SQL
- Database: SQL Server, MongoDB, RavenDB
- Server-side Frameworks: REST, gRPC, JWT, CQRS, MediatR
- Server side France volus. NEST, girl C, 5 vi 1, CQRS, Fredikir
- Client-side Technologies: JavaScript, jQuery, PWA, Ajax, JSON, Knockout, HTML, CSS
- Version Control: TFS, Git
- Tools: Jira, OTRS
- Other: Redis, Elasticsearch, RediSearch, Entity Framework Core, Dapper, Clean Architecture

Licenses & Certifications

- SQL Server 2005 Sematec
- C# LinkedIn Assessments
- .Net Framework LinkedIn Assessments
- Transaction-SQL (T-SQL) LinkedIn Assessments
- Clean Code in Asp.Net Core <u>TopLearn.com</u>

Languages

English: Limited working proficiency

Turkish: Elementary proficiency

Germany: Elementary proficiency (A1) Persian: Native